<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_name">Space Launch Now</string>
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_showIcon">true</string>
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_showVersion">true</string>
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_text">
        <![CDATA[Keep up to date on all your favorite spaceflight missions from around the world.<br/>]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Just remove those entries if you don't want to use a special button with a text within your about this app view :D -->
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_special1_name">EULA</string>
    <string name="aboutLibraries_description_special1_text"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Space Launch Now 1.0.1</h1>
<h1>Copyright © 2016 Caleb Jones</h1>

<p>
*** END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT ***
</p>

<p>
IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.
</p>

<h2>1. LICENSE</h2>

<p>
By receiving, opening the file package, and/or using Space Launch Now 1.0.1("Software") containing this software, you agree that this End User User License Agreement(EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
</p>

<p>
Unless you have a different license agreement signed by Caleb Jones your use of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.
</p>

<p>
Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Caleb Jones grants to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use Space Launch Now 1.0.1 in accordance with this Agreement and any other written agreement with Caleb Jones. Caleb Jones does not transfer the title of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 to you; the license granted to you is not a sale. This agreement is a binding legal agreement between Caleb Jones and the purchasers or users of Space Launch Now 1.0.1.
</p>

<p>
If you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove Space Launch Now 1.0.1 from your computer now and, if applicable, promptly return to Caleb Jones by mail any copies of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 and related documentation and packaging in your possession.
</p>

<h2>2. DISTRIBUTION</h2>

<p>
Space Launch Now 1.0.1 and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed, re-sold, offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you may make one copy for archive purposes only. For information about redistribution of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 contact Caleb Jones.
</p>

<h2>3. USER AGREEMENT</h2>

<h3>3.1 Use</h3>

<p>
Your license to use Space Launch Now 1.0.1 is limited to the number of licenses purchased by you. You shall not allow others to use, copy or evaluate copies of Space Launch Now 1.0.1.
</p>

<h3>3.2 Use Restrictions</h3>

<p>
You shall use Space Launch Now 1.0.1 in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful purpose. Without limiting the foregoing, use, display or distribution of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 together with material that is pornographic, racist, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, libelous, abusive, promoting hatred, discriminating or displaying prejudice based on religion, ethnic heritage, race, sexual orientation or age is strictly prohibited.
</p>

<p>
Each licensed copy of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 may be used on one single computer location by one user. Use of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 means that you have loaded, installed, or run Space Launch Now 1.0.1 on a computer or similar device. If you install Space Launch Now 1.0.1 onto a multi-user platform, server or network, each and every individual user of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 must be licensed separately.
</p>

<p>
You may make one copy of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 for backup purposes, providing you only have one copy installed on one computer being used by one person. Other users may not use your copy of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 . The assignment, sublicense, networking, sale, or distribution of copies of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 are strictly forbidden without the prior written consent of Caleb Jones. It is a violation of this agreement to assign, sell, share, loan, rent, lease, borrow, network or transfer the use of Space Launch Now 1.0.1. If any person other than yourself uses Space Launch Now 1.0.1 registered in your name, regardless of whether it is at the same time or different times, then this agreement is being violated and you are responsible for that violation!
</p>

<h3>3.3 Copyright Restriction</h3>

<p>
This Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble or decompile Space Launch Now 1.0.1. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are based upon or derived from Space Launch Now 1.0.1 in whole or in part.
</p>

</p>
Caleb Jones\'s name, logo and graphics file that represents Space Launch Now 1.0.1 shall not be used in any way to promote products developed with Space Launch Now 1.0.1 . Caleb Jones retains sole and exclusive ownership of all right, title and interest in and to Space Launch Now 1.0.1 and all Intellectual Property rights relating thereto.
</p>

</p>
Copyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of Space Launch Now 1.0.1, products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample, or text may be copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the bounds of the single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are reserved for Caleb Jones.
</p>

<h3>3.4 Limitation of Responsibility</h3>

<p>
You will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Caleb Jones , its employees, agents and distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or in any way connected with your use of Caleb Jones\'s Software.
</p>

<p>
In no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will Caleb Jones , its employees, agents or distributors be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss of information or data, or pecuniary loss), in connection with or arising out of or related to this Agreement, Space Launch Now 1.0.1 or the use or inability to use Space Launch Now 1.0.1 or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters hereunder whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.
</p>

<p>
Caleb Jones\'s entire liability, without exception, is limited to the customers\' reimbursement of the purchase price of the Software (maximum being the lesser of the amount paid by you and the suggested retail price as listed by Caleb Jones ) in exchange for the return of the product, all copies, registration papers and manuals, and all materials that constitute a transfer of license from the customer back to Caleb Jones.
</p>

<h3>3.5 Warranties</h3>

<p>
Except as expressly stated in writing, Caleb Jones makes no representation or warranties in respect of this Software and expressly excludes all other warranties, expressed or implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.
</p>

<h3>3.6 Governing Law</h3>

<p>
This Agreement shall be governed by the law of the United States applicable therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of United States therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.
</p>

<h3>3.7 Termination</h3>

<p>
Any failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 and destroy all copies of Space Launch Now 1.0.1 supplied under this Agreement. The financial obligations incurred by you shall survive the expiration or termination of this license.
</p>

<h2>4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY</h2>

<p>
THIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY Space Launch Now 1.0.1 AS WELL.
</p>

<h2>5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA</h2>

<p>
You agree that Caleb Jones may collect and use information gathered in any manner as part of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to Space Launch Now 1.0.1.Caleb Jones may also use this information to provide notices to you which may be of use or interest to you.
</p>
    ]]></string>

</resources>
