<resources>
  <string name="application_name">Space Launch Now</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="status_go">"Go for Launch"</string>
  <string name="status_nogo">"Launch is NO GO"</string>
  <string name="status_success">"Launch was Successful"</string>
  <string name="status_failure">"Launch Failure Occurred"</string>
  <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="spacex_summary">SpaceX designs, manufactures and launches advanced rockets and spacecraft. The company was founded in 2002 to revolutionize space technology, with the ultimate goal of enabling people to live on other planets.</string>
  <string name="usaf_summary">The United States Air Force is the aerial warfare service branch of the United States Armed Forces and one of the seven American uniformed services.</string>
  <string name="casc_summary">The China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation(CASC) is the main contractor for the Chinese space program. It is state-owned and has a number of subordinate entities which design, develop and manufacture a range of spacecraft, launchCategory vehicles, strategic and tactical missile systems, and ground equipment.</string>
  <string name="cnsa_summary">The China National Space Administration (CNSA) is the national space agency of the People\'s Republic of China. It is responsible for the national space program and for planning and development of space activities.</string>
  <string name="isro_summary">The Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO), is the space agency of the Indian government headquartered in the city of Bengaluru. Its vision is to \"harness space technology for national development, while pursuing space science research and planetary exploration\".</string>
  <string name="vko_summary">"The Russian Aerospace Defence Forces (VKO) was the branch of the Armed Forces of the Russian Federation responsible for air and missile defence, and the operation of Russian military satellites and the Plesetsk Cosmodrome. "</string>
  <string name="roscosmos_summary">The Roscosmos State Corporation for Space Activities, commonly known as Roscosmos, is the governmental body responsible for the Russian space science program and general aerospace research.</string>
  <string name="ula_summary"><![CDATA[United Launch Alliance (ULA) is a joint venture of Lockheed Martin Space Systems and Boeing Defense, Space & Security. ULA was formed in December 2006 by combining the teams at these companies which provide spacecraft launchCategory services to the government of the United States.]]></string>
  <string name="gd_summary">General Dynamics Corporation is an American aerospace and defense company formed by mergers and divestitures. It is the world\'s fifth-largest defense contractor based on 2012 revenues.</string>
  <string name="asa_summary">Arianespace SA is a French multinational company founded in 1980 as the world\'s first commercial launchCategory service provider.</string>
  <string name="TsSKB_summary">The Progress State Research and Production Space Centre, also known as TsSKB-Progress, is a Russian \"Federal State Unitary Enterprise\" under the jurisdiction of Roscosmos, the Russian Federal Space Agency responsible for space science and aerospace research. It is the developer of the famous Soyuz-FG rocket used for manned space flight, as well as Soyuz-U used for launching unmanned probes.</string>
  <string name="nasa_summary">The National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) is the United States government agency responsible for the civilian space program as well as aeronautics and aerospace research.</string>

  <string name="spacex_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950103/3BqROn0_pfsamc.jpg</string>
  <string name="Yuzhnoye_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950107/KnDMy7l_ua9lnu.png</string>
  <string name="usa_flag">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950350/usa_flag_pewvgy.png</string>
  <string name="ula_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950111/rh7JAa3_ygosxx.jpg</string>
  <string name="rus_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950119/eafUB5i_iatgl1.png</string>
  <string name="chn_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950120/dIsaknI_qcvxuy.png</string>
  <string name="ind_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950125/Caj9kpG_xo8s1g.png</string>
  <string name="jpn_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950129/QOdDYa5_dhdlct.png</string>
  <string name="ariane_logo">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1454950133/yffq0aI_oyyhmj.jpg</string>
  <string name="title_activity_debug">DebugActivity</string>
  <string name="general_settings_for_launch_tracking_and_application_behavior">General settings for launch tracking and application behavior</string>
  <string name="whats_new_content">Changelog\n
\n· New ways to share launches with the official https://spacelaunchnow.me.
\n· Fully reworked and customizable widgets for Supporters - more to come!
\n· Remove all local alarms, services and wakelocks in favor of using Evernotes Job library.
\n· Improved battery life with server-side notifications with Android 8.0 support.
\n· Updated on-boarding and initial application configuration.
\n· Reduced network and local storage (90% reduced - usage.
\n· A plethora of bugfixes - crashes, UI, non-fatals… blah blah.</string>
  <string name="link_feedback">https://www.reddit.com/r/spacelaunchnow</string>
  <string name="link_store">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=me.calebjones.spacelaunchnow</string>

  <string name="title_activity_fullscreen_image">Image Viewer</string>

  <string name="supporter_title">Become a Supporter</string>

  <string name="supporter_description">Help ensure continued support, timely bug fixes, and new features.</string>
  <string name="supporter_features">\u2022Current weather forecast for launch pads.\n\u2022Historical weather forecast for past launches.\n\u2022Automatically sync upcoming launches to your calendar.\n\u2022Dynamic pictures of launch vehicles as watch face background.\n</string>

  <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
  <string name="title_activity_download">Download</string>
  <string name="title_activity_web_view_fallback">Space Launch Now</string>
  <string name="slide_one_title">Space Launch Now</string>

  <string name="slide_one_description">Keep up to date on all your favorite orbital launches, missions, and launch vehicles.</string>

  <string name="slide_two_title">Notification for Launches</string>
  <string name="slide_two_description">Get notifications for upcoming launches and look into the history of spaceflight</string>
  <string name="slide_three_title">Find Launch Vehicles</string>
  <string name="slide_three_description">Get to know the vehicles that have taken us to orbit.</string>
  <string name="default_wear_image">http://res.cloudinary.com/dnkkbfy3m/image/upload/v1462465326/navbar_one_sqfhes.png</string>
  <string name="thank_you">This application, Space Launch Now, started as a simple weekend project. In the course of a year its grown to nearly 10,000 active users. I am incredibly appreciative to everyone that has taken the time to report bugs, give feedback, participate in BETA\'s and become supporters.</string>
  <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
  <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
  <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
  <string name="app_name">Gene-rate</string>
  <string name="please_rate">Hey there! You seem to like this app, would you mind visiting the Play Store and give a rating? It would help us a great deal!
    \n\nIf instead you hate this app, we would love to hear your feedback so we can improve. Thanks!</string>
  <string name="please_rate_short">Hey, you seem to like this app. You would help us a great deal with a 5-star rating! Otherwise if you have suggestions - please let us know.</string>
  <string name="button_yes">Rate!</string>
  <string name="button_no">No thanks</string>
  <string name="button_feedback">Give Feedback</string>
  <string name="button_dont_ask">Don’t ask again</string>
  <string name="swipe_to_dismiss">Swipe to Dismiss</string>
</resources>
